simpledns.com 2006-11-03

# Simple DNS Plus - Privacy Policy

This document details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

**INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED  
**In order to determine what services, topics, and individual web pages are the most popular, we keep track of the pages visited within our web site and the use of some of the links to external web sites.  
We log and use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information.  
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, and for keeping track of user sessions in sections of the web-site that require a login.  
A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  
If you choose to decline cookies, you will not be able to purchase our software online, and may not be able to fully experience other interactive features of our web site. 

**USE OF E-MAIL ADDRESSES / OPT OUT  
**If you contact us by e-mail, purchase our software, or subscribe to our mailing list, we may occasionally use your e-mail address to send you information about product updates and other news we feel you might be interested in (typically only when a new software version is released).  
Any automated e-mails sent will include instructions for automatic removal from our mailing list.  
You may also opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time by sending an e-mail to [support@jhsoft.com](mailto:support@jhsoft.com) asking us to remove you from our list.. 

**USE OF ORDER/REGISTRATION INFORMATION  
**When you place an order (register), we requests information such as contact information, credit card number and demographic information. The contact information you provide is used to send you orders, and provide you with updates on future releases of our products.  
You can opt out at any time (see above).  
If you purchase by credit card, your contact information is also used to verify the validity of the credit card used.  
Your financial information (like credit card number) is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. 

**DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES**  
JH Software does not provide, sell, rent or lease its customer lists (including e-mail lists) to third parties  
We will only disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on JH Software; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of JH Software; (c) defend payment disputes (to banks / credit card companies); and, (d) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of JH Software's web site or products.

**SECURITY  
**JH Software secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.  
We secure the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.  
Order/registration information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted through the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted protection.  
We use Microsoft web server software which is continuously updated with the latest security patches.  
We do not store credit card numbers on any computers connected directly or indirectly to the Internet.

**CHILDREN'S GUIDELINES  
**We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.

**DISCLAIMER**  
This site contains links to other sites. JH Software is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

**CONTACT US**  
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@jhsoft.com](mailto:support@jhsoft.com)

For more information, please see Terms of Use
